http://www.usmilitaryart.com/privacy-policy

Contact Us
All Categories:
Start typing and press Enter to search
Follow us on social media...
Shopping Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Career Montages
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Privacy Policy
SAFEGUARDING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Any information obtained by US Military Art .com is for our own exclusive use in communicating with our customers. We do not sell, copy, or otherwise distribute client information. We reserve the right from time to time to contact our current and former clients to make them aware of special offers from US Military Art .com, but we have no partners or marketing firms authorized to contact clients on our behalf.
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately
